(Raj:)I'm heartbroken
and you're hitting on me?
(Penny:)What? No.
(Raj:)Look, Penny, you're great,
but I had a long talk with my parents.
And they said if I date an lndian girl,
I get a Maserati.
(Raj:)Mm, oh, cheesecake,
you're just as good as a woman...
(Raj:)...even though I can't have sex
with you.
(Howard:)Try throwing it in the microwave
for a few seconds.
Should I use the restroom
or wait until we get home?
(Sheldon:)Come on,
Papa needs to void his bladder.
Oh, that's not what you wanna see
after three buttermilks.
(Penny:)Here you go, boys.
I'll pick it up when you're ready.
- Thanks for dinner, buddy.
- Yeah, real big of you.
(Sheldon:)Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Oh, don't cheap out on the tip.
We all know you're loaded now.